and what’s going on there is an offensive,
а что вде происходит это наступ просто
you’re just interrupting all the time, it’s called
вы перебивайте постоянно это называется
running in the strategy, I
обкатка стратегии
remember everything about your
всё помню ваш про
frying room, can’t you tell
жарочная не подскажете интересует
me? I’m interested in what you’re interested in specifically,
Меня А что вас интересует конкретно ну
well, I saw what Western
как вот я видел что публикуют западные
experts publish Yes, according to photo and video documents What do
специалисты Да по фото-видео докам Что
you have today, more than 200  units of
за сегодня у вас более 200 единиц
armored vehicles
бронетехники
were lost Well, it’s some kind of rush that doesn’t
потеряно Ну это какой-то гон такого не
happen there, the columns are just so
бывает там там прямо колонны такие
broken Well, the columns Maybe, but it
разбитые Ну колонны Может быть но такого
doesn’t happen that there are just 200
не бывает что прямо 200
units Not a tank, well, with an armored personnel carrier there are also
единиц Не танко ну с бпшка ещё там
other armored vehicles Well, it’s possible
другими бронетехники Ну возможно и
that not a lot is lost if it’s me  I
что не сколько потеряно если вот это я
don’t know, I don’t know, I don’t know, I don’t know, what I
не знаю я не знаю Поня а не знаю то что
see is that you just asked a question. Do
я вижу вы просто это ну вопрос задали А
you want to hear the answer that there
вы что хотите ответ услышать что там с
is no counter-attack with the counter-attack, like,
контрнаступ нет никакого контрнаступ как
well, you were in the water in the
Ну вы на в воде ки сунулись в
counter-attack, so I understood it or not, no, no
контрнаступ так я понял или нет нет
one  the outline of the crust poked its head in. And what is
никто не сунулся контур наст А что в
happening in Avdeevka is an offensive, you just
Авдеевке происходит это наступ просто вы
interrupt all the time, it’s called
перебивайте постоянно это называется
running in the strategy,
обкатка стратегии
everything is fine. How many
всё хорошо Сколько сколько личного
personnel and armored vehicles to run into this
состава и бронетехники обкатать в эту
strategy, can you tell me from your
стратегию можете мне сказать по вашим
data? I don’t know, you don’t know,
данным Я не знаю не знаете
but you’re smiling. No, I don’t understand, you  you
а сам улыбается Не а я не понимаю вы так
’re smiling like that, just last time You’re so
улыбаетесь просто в прошлый раз Вы такой
serious about it
серьёзный
Andryushenka means Look, I just
Андрюшенька значит Смотри я вот
looked Yes, you’re talking about the contour of
посмотрел Да ты говоришь на контур
your attack, something you’ve been completely rock bottom in 4 months
наступ ваш что-то у вас за 4 месяца
Why do you think that the
полное дно Почему ты думаешь что у
Russian army in the new conditions should have
российской армии в новых условиях должно
had something  it will turn out
что-то было получиться
right away if you have a complete bottom with everything
сходу если у вас полное дно со всем
Western with consultants, generals with
западными с консультантами генералами со
everything else, so show me You are like a
всем остальным так покажите Вот вы как
good FSB agent Show that we
хороший фсбшник по Покажите чтобы у нас
have at least on some day such losses
были Хоть в какой-то день такие потери
How do you have on a
Как у вас в
day right now show Yes, show
день прямо сейчас показать Да покажите
not just well  for your audience it
не просто ну для вашей аудитории это
will be
будет
traumatic Yes, on what day we
травматика Да вот в какой день мы
lost as much as you today under
потеряли столько сколько вы сегодня под
Avdeevka Let’s give you why, I
авдеевкой Давайте вам Зачем сколько я
don’t even know how many people you lost,
даже не знаю сколько по надеев потеряли
you’re telling me now, well, let me tell you,
вы сейчас мне говорите ну давайте мнете
I’m saying that today you lost
я говорю что вы сегодня потеряли
more than 200 armored vehicles alone Yes and  more than a
более 200 бронетехники едини Да и более
thousand
тысячи личного
personnel dead and wounded, well, something
состава мёртвыми и раненными ну что-то м
tells me that the year is generally full,
подсказывает чтото год вообще гон полный
because well, I can’t imagine what
потому что ну я не представляю себе что
was supposed to happen, what, let me read
должно было случиться что давайте я
your military core, here Parker
вашего воен кора почитаю вот Паркер те
writes in here, lays out a map, Taryn
пишет в вот карту выкладывает тарин
took read pa writes in  Avdeevka at
взяли читайте па пишет в Авдеевке на
the moment really has nothing to
данный момент вот так на самом деле
brag about, especially so far it
хвастаться особенно пока нечем
has finally managed to gain a foothold on the
окончательно удалось закрепиться на
well-known waste heap and on this, please,
известном терриконе и на этом пожалуйста
all the equipment is lost guard of people,
всё технике потеряно караул людей
too, there are no problems known until you
тоже нело пробле известны пока не
sort out the elements of the
разбери с элементами
scrape. Well, what next do you want to
передряги Ну а что дальше Вы хотите
say, you just took a certain fact of everything
сказать просто взял некий факт всего
I don’t hear a lot about anything
много про я не слышу Ничего
Treasures are being posted, it’s confirmed, then everything is
клады выкладывают подтверждён то все на
being filmed Come on now, this is
видео снимается Давай вы меня сечас это
what it’s called, we’re discussing the seed with Mito,
как его называется семя обсуждаем с мито
but I’m not laughing at all because
ж во я вообще не я ржу потому что и в
last time you were somehow more impudent
прошлый раз Вы какой-то более дерзкий
yes And now it’s already  Laugh yourself, let's
были да А сейчас аж сами ржёте давайте
move on, then look, there is
давайте дальше значит смотрите есть
such a thing, there is such a thing as what is it
такая вещь есть такая вещь как как это
called, what is the best name for it Yes,
называется как это лучше назвать Да
strategy, tactics, you know, but no stinks, stinks
стратегия тактика знаете а нет вони вони
change and change, so what is the
меняются а меняется менятся так то в чём
strategy like wasting so much of your
стратегия типа угробить столько своей
personal power, in short, under Avdeev Here it is
личной силы короче под Авдеев Вот ещё
again  I’ll tell you, you don’t know Why,
раз расскажу те вы не знаете Да почему
I don’t understand why the Ukrainian
вот я наме не понимаю зачем украинская
army carried out a
армия 4 месяца добилась в
counter-offensive for 4 months, I explain Yes, I explain
контрнаступление объясняю Да объясняю
Look,
Смотри я вам объясню Сколько было кон не
I’ll explain to you How long it was, I won’t explain to you, no matter how long there was a
объясню не я вам сколько бы сколько был
counter-offensive, when Kherson was
контрнаступ когда был Херсон
taken, something took a long time there  Also,
взят там что-то долго было тоже вот
Kherson was taken on November 11th, so it
Херсон взяли 11 этого ноября так
started at least in the beginning of summer.
началось как минимум в начале лета Так
So, there was a counter-offensive for 5 months before they
то есть 5 месяцев шёл контрнаступ пока
took Kherson. Nobody broke into
взяли Херсон Никто же не ломился в
Kherson. Yes, they knocked out a counter-offensive, so they’re
Херсон Да выбивали контрнаступ это что
running away. Hurray. They knocked out their bases and
это они бегут Ура Это выбивали ши базы
logistics routes, and then you
логистические пути а потом вы
run away and  so that is, the counter-offensive now
убегает и так то есть контрнаступ сейчас
in the Zaporozhye direction is going less
на запорожском направлении идёт меньше
than last year in Kherso, what are
чем в прошлом году на херсо что вообще
you doing at all, yes, of course you are a strategist
вы что-то вообще да вы конечно стратег
from God, I’ll tell you, let’s tell you, as a
от Бога я вам скажу давайте так вы как
strategist, you can remember some
стратег можете вспомните какой-то
serious battle in the Kherson region
серьёзный бой в Херсонской области в
last year  some kind of huge serious
прошлом году огромный какой-то серьёзный
battle Yes, there was a serious mess there at the very beginning,
бой Да там серьёзно там в само начала
no no. For example, within the
начался замес не не Вот например в
framework of the Ukrainian counter-offensive, a
рамках украинского контрнаступ на
week ago, after Kherson was liberated,
неделю назад уже как освободили Херсон
you can say how Kherson was liberated.
можете сказать как освободили
Kherson. Well, they created certain
Херсон Херсон Ну создали определённые
problems with logistics. So, due to these
проблемы с логистикой Вот и за счёт этих
problems, they squeezed out how  about called
проблем выдавили как о называется
forced the same thing is now being done in
вынудили тоже самое сейчас делается в
a counter-offensive in the Zaporozhye direction
контрнаступ на запорожском направлении
What happened to the airfield in
Что у вас случилось с аэродромом в
Berdyansk can you imagine
Бердянске представляете вы представляете
What is it you don’t jump from topic to
Что такое вы не перепрыгивать с темы на
topic I’m not
тему Не я вам
looking at you You confirmed with your mouth Yes
смотрите Вы своим ртом подтвердили Да
that Ukraine you knocked out your
что Украина вы выбивала ваши
logistics bases and forced  it’s
логистические базы и вынудила вас
shameful for you to run away from Kherson now the
убежать из Херсона позорно теперь тоже
same thing is happening now in the
само тоже самое происходит сейчас на
Zaporozhye direction a couple of days ago
запорожском направлении пару дней назад
American missiles Yes, with cluster
американская ракетам Да с кассетным
munitions, they
боеприпасам расфигачечная
knocked out 11 of your helicopters at the airfield with one blow
одним ударом выбили на аэродроме 11
Yes, this is knocking out, is there
ваших вертолётов Да это есть выбивание
a counterattack or
это есть контрнаступ или
not, well, I would say this is a good mine
нет это ну я бы сказал это хорошая мина
if the game is bad, you’re a fool, well, Ponya That is, it
при плохой игре дура ну ла Поня То есть
turns out It’s just that you are the same again,
получается Просто вы те опять
you’re always interrupting me all the time,
жере вы всё время перебивает я всё время
I’m overtaking you, you understand now over
перева Я доминирую понимаете сейчас над
you Yes, because I’m like Ukraine, I’m
вами Да потому что я как Украина я Жар
hot, in short, you’re growing up, you understand ro T Ukra, you’re ours, you
короче рос понимаете ро Т Укра вы наш вы
were looking for something you wanted there  tell me
там искали чтото хотели мне рассказать
Show my entire audience when
Покажите всей моей аудитории когда
Ukraine lost as much in a day as
Украина потеряла за день столько сколько
you did under Avdeevka, that’s really how much
вы под авдеевкой реально вот сколько
Zaporizhzhya Front Yes, there is a counterattack, what are
Запорожский фронт Да идёт контрнаступ
you doing there, how many people are you killing
что вы там сколько вы убиваете людей
like armored vehicles per day Show us
типа бронетехники в день Покажите нам
now some stupid things, I understand
сечас какие-то глупости понима Ну покажи
Well, show me Look, you’re saying that  In short, there’s
Вот смотри ты говоришь что короче там
nothing there, and there’s even no flag, oh sad thing, it’s
чтото нету да даже есть нету флага о
true,
печалька правда
but it’s not there, it’s just that the corpses are all yours, so there are
а не не там просто у трупы сплошные ваши
corpses there, there are corpses.
чтов нет поэтому Ну там трупы там трупы
It doesn’t show how many people were killed. Well, they
Это же не показывает сколько Да убито Ну
removed one trench and that’s it. But how many really is the whole
сняли один окоп и всё А сколько реально
point, I want you  just to
всё дело я вам хочу об этом как раз
say this, it doesn’t show how many were
сказать этоже не показывает сколько там
actually killed there
реально убито
Yes, there is a website or look there is a website or
Да вот есть сайт or смотри есть сайт or
Yes, between Naro they all
Да между Наро они все вот эти видео
collect these videos, they count everyone Yes they
коллекционируют считают каждого Да
count when all the locations Well, no, not
считают когда всё локации Ну нене не
the phone Give it back, find it, look it up,
телефон Верни же найди найди Ну смотри
look it up if  goes if there is a
езна смотри если идёт если идёт
counter-offensive of Ukraine for how many months?
контрнаступ Украины сколько месяцев У
You should already have evidence
вас же уже должны быть доказательства
of how much you destroyed there, killed and so on. Further
сколько вы там уничтожили убили и так
how much is this normal? Well, this is the
Дале сколько что это нормально Ну это го
city of Khmelnitsky Well, this is the city of
это город Хмельницкий Ну так это город
Khmelnitsky I saw and what’s up with since the
Хмельницкий Я видел и что там с с
fourteenth year Yes people Well
четырнадцатого года Да люди Ну и
that from the year 1914 yes they
что года с с четырнадцатого года да
bury there I can’t read yours there,
хоронят там я не могу почитать там ваших
I get
немерено я получать
tens of thousands of years and what’s wrong
года десятки тысяч и что не не так
show me Well, show me back, I was in this
покажи Ну так покажи назад я на этом
cemetery, I buried my friends there
кладбище был я же там знакомых хоронил
Well, show me also what, well, what are you  you want
Ну покажи ещё и что ну ну что ты хочешь
9 years in 9 years, people who could have mogi Well,
9 лет за 9 лет люди которые моги моги Ну
9 years Yes, look again at this cemetery
9 лет Да вот смотри ещё раз это кладбище
in the city of Khmelnitsky Yes, 9 years,
в городе Хмельницком Да 9 лет ты
look there on the graves there is a date the date they
посмотри там есть на могилах дата дата
died that year fifteen
когда умерли тый год пятнадцатый
sixteenth Yes, people who fought
шестнадцатый Да люди которые воевали
like yes
типа да
So show me, let's aunt  these
Так покажи давай теть эти
Dawa koro Well, show me, you wanted to
Дава коро Ну покажи ты меня хотел
scare me, the cemetery is my city No, show
напугать кладбище мои горо Нет покажи
it Let's agree on the cemetery
это Давай мы договорим про кладбище
Look at the dates, the dates there are fresh
Посмотри даты даты какие там есть свежий
and have been there since the fourteenth year Yes, there are
и есть с четырнадцатого года Да там люди
military people who have been with us since the fourteenth
военные которые у нас с четырнадцатого
year of all the military, Even if he is not in
года всех военных Даже если он не в
combat  he was killed in actions Yes, he was buried
боевых действиях погиб Да его хоронили
since he was a military man and they buried him with a flag
раз он военный да хоронили с флагом
there he is, for example, on this straight
там он есть например вот на этой прямо
alley where there is this is where this grandmother
алее где есть вот где эта бабушка
passed Yes there
проходила Да там
is
есть
that in one battle your equipment died
что в одном бою погибшая техника ваша
How many in one od bo 4 5 6 at least I
Сколько в одно од бо 4 5 6 как минимум Я
only  I see six, yes, that is, in one day,
только ше вижу шесть да то есть за день
you killed six. Well, how much
Вы шесть убили Ну сколько сколько
equipment do you have per day? Well, I just
техники вы в день Ну вот я просто Одну
looked at one, let’s look, you’re showing
посмотрел давай смотри ты показываешь
some Photos, look, just
какие-то Фотографии смотри просто
photos. You can, let me go to the
фотографии Вот можеш давай я захожу на
website. Let’s open the site, you’re on fire, I’m the only one
Да давай откроем сайт ты горишь одно я
other let's look at the site what they say and Andry come on You're
другое давай посмотрим сайт что они гово
a brake Andryush why is this kiu
пож Андрю давай Ты тормоз Андрюш зачем
I want s ri let's look like
это киу я тея хочу с ри давай так смотри
you and I now we're
мы сейчас с тобой мы с тобой сейчас
looking at the data Oh come on let's look what
смотрим даны О давай давай смотри что
it is szhi
такое такое
don't know What is Oks Yes I know  this is
сжи не знаеш Что такое Окс Да знаю я это
Ox Lord, what is
Окс Господи ну что
it? Well, this is a site they collect, like
такое Ну это сайтом они собирают типа
damn, it’s called counting
блин это называется считают потери
equipment losses and so on, let’s say
технику и так далее давай
maybe 3 days ago, now we’re
так вот 3 дня назад так сейчас сечас
looking at such abnormally large losses, you
смотрим так аномально большие потери вы
destroyed 11 of the RF equipment oryx,
свв уничтожили 11 из техники РФ орикс
this was not 3 days ago  not this in 3 days
это 3 дня назад было не не это за 3 дня
This is 3 days This is not fresh, so I’m
Это 3 дня Это не свежее вот я тебе
telling you what, and
говорю то что вот и
so this means 118 units of
так вот вот значит 118 единиц техники
Russian equipment against 25 of Ukraine, so you
России против 25 Украины вот ты мне
show me five dead and five
показываешь пять погибших а пять
damaged armored vehicles And how many of yours
подбитый бронетехники А сколько ваших
were knocked out and here they are summing it all up  11
было подбито а вот они всё сводят 11
units were Russian 25 Ukrainian then
единиц было Российская 25 украинская то
who is grinding whom,
кто кого перемалывает
here are the total losses it was from
вот вот общие потери это было с 10 по 16
October 10 to 16 118 units, the total losses of
октября 118 единиц вот общие потери
Russia in equipment from October 10 to 16
России в технике с 10 по 16 октября
amounted to 118 units among them 27 tanks
составили 118 единиц среди них 27 танков
33 infantry fighting vehicles eight armored personnel
33 боевых машины пехоты восемь
carriers in total from the beginning
бронетранспортёра всего с начала
Ukrainian counter-offensive in June The
украинского контрнаступления в июне
Russian army lost 2.73 units of
Российская армия потеряла 2.73 единицы
equipment, among them 386 tanks 499 infantry fighting vehicles 113 armored personnel
техники среди них 386 танков 499 БМП 113
carriers, this is not all in words This is
БТР это всё не на словах Это каждое э
just something that was confirmed by a video or photo
только то что подтвердили видео или фото
specifically linked to the IOC terrain They took Moscow, they
конкретно с привязкой к местности МОК
took it Why do we
Взяли москву-то Взяли А зачем нам Моск
need Moscow sconces  Well they took it in 3 days look
бра вы ж ки взяли за 3 дня смотри
tyr Wait wait No you are running away we
тыр Подожди подожди Нет ты убегаешь мы
Come on now we are comparing you
Давай мы сейчас тебя доком по сравнению
now let’s do that we want to compare We want to
давай так мы хотим сравнить Мы хотим
compare the losses of Ukraine and Russia who has
сравнить потери Украины и России у кого
more losses So tell me who has more losses
больше потери Вот скажи у кого больше
so you are like an FSB agent Tell me who has more losses
потери вот ты как фсбшник Скажи у кого
losses in manpower and equipment losses in what
потери в живой силе и техни потери в чём
in manpower And in artillery technology
в живой силе И в технике артиллерии у
in your artillery With us you have Dawa on
вас в артиллерии У нас у вас Дава на
the basis of what Read on the basis of
основании чего Прочитай на основании
what what international source
чего какой международный источник Да
Yes speak Well, I just
говори Ну просто я вот так
decided like this You eat the blunder and I rely  on the
решил Вот ты ляпа ешь а я опираюсь на
very thing you are doing now No, look,
самое что ты сейчас делаешь Нет я смотри
I’ll tell you Take it, take it, read
я тебе Возьми Зачитай возьми Зачитай
some authoritative source where they
какой-то авторитетный источник где
say that in Ukraine there are more losses in
говорят что в Украины больше потери в
artillery. On the contrary, I’ll read to you now about
артиллерии Наоборот я тебе сейчас про
artillery Yes,
артиллерию прочитаю Да
losses You still have yours Ministry of Defense
потери Ты ещё своё Министерство обороны
to me Read it, tell me I’m not telling you mine  and
мне Почитай скажи я не говорю своё и
your Ministry they understand they
твоё Министерство они понимаешь они
can
могут
raise Well of course yes They can’t
повышать Ну конечно да Всё не могут те
tell everything, look it’s very simple
рассказывать вот смотри это очень просто
Google everything is losses Yes, the losses of the parties
Google всё есть потери Да потери сторон
during the period of Russia’s marriage to Ukraine, it’s
в период жения России на Украину вот
just that everything is,
просто всё есть
so the fresh losses of Russian
так вот свежая потери российской
artillery in Zaporozhye are five times higher
артиллерии в Запорожье в пять раз выше
What will
чем
Moscow give to the Ukrainians? They haven’t taken it yet. Tell me, why do
даст Моск ещ не взяли Скажи зачем мы же
n’t we look
не ещё раз смотри
again? Wait, let’s not jump over
раз Подожди Давай так не не перепрыгина
the topic. Let’s give you the ratio of losses, I’ll
тему Давай соотношение потерь я тебя
finish you off by the ratio of losses. You admit,
добью по соотношения потерь Ты признаёшь
look, you admit that Russia’s losses are
смотри ты признаёшь что потери России
many times greater than the losses of Ukraine,
кратно превосходят потери Украины
I admit it to you
признаёшь я тебе ещё
again. Well  what about the question again, look
раз Ну как лу чего вопро ещё раз смотри
again, I didn’t come up with it, I’m not reading
ещё раз не я придумал не я тебе читаю
international authoritative analysts for you.
международные авторитетные аналитики Да
Yes, according to Oryx, I told you from
вот по орикс Я тебе сказал с дего по 16
16,118 units of armored vehicles against 25
118 единиц бронетехники против 25
Ukrainian ones, this is confirmed on their
украинско это подтверждённый у них на
website, I
сайте каждая
’ll read each support, come here
сопровождения прочитаю
Listen, if there  they are rolling out their
вот Слушай если там раскатывают их
equipment. Excuse me, Western, that they
технику Извини меня западную что они
will tell you right again,
тебе будут прав-то рассказывать ещё раз
look
смотри ещё
again, you can, if this is crap, then you
раз Вы можете ес если это лажа вы тогда
show it, look, here we
показываете смотрите вот мы Вам
show you the list. This decides, tell
показываем список Вот это решает скажи
me, this decides not because look, you are
мне это решае не потому что смотри ты
running away, you are all  Russian babbles
убегаешь ты вы все россиян ские балаболы
are feeding you [ __ ] propaganda
вас кормят говном пропагандистский да то
yes that's what decides let's so who is
так что решает давай так кто кого
grinding whom Ukraine Russia or Russia
перемалывает Украина Россию или Россия
Ukraine some strange question Zakho
Украину какой-то странный вопрос Зак хо
Whose losses in people and equipment
Чьи потери Чьи потери в людях и техники
are greater in the people of Ukraine Exactly more
больше в людях Украины Точно больше как
on what basis say on the basis  why
на основании чего скажи на основани чего
Show me at least one source that
Покажи мне хоть один источник который
compares the losses in people of Ukraine and Russia
сравнит потери в людях Украины и России
Show Douglas McGregor
Покажи Дуглас МакГрегор
American on the basis of what he says
американский на основани чего он говори
the President of the United States on the basis of what Dougs Magre let's
Президента США на основании чего дугс
read Read me the news let's
магре давай прочита Прочитай мне новость
figure it out now maybe it
давай вот сейчас мы разберём может
really can Let's read what
действительно может Давай прочитай что
Douglas Madre says on  based on what the
говорит Дуглас мадре на основании чего
buzz is I like to roll out
кайф Люблю раскатывать
read come on come on let's read Let's
читай давай давай давай давай почитай
try to come up with what I was
Покачи уже придумать то на что я
referring to I read what you are
ссылался я прочитал то на что ты
referring to You
ссылается Ты
read it somehow strange yes in technology
прочитай как-то странно да в технике
Ukraine is five times In short it fry like
Украина в пять раз Короче жарит типа
Russia And in people they come from somewhere
Россию А в людях откуда-то берутся
big
большие
losses Well, once again, Russia has more equipment.
потери Ну ещё раз техники у России
The truth is lost. Which is not always true, or technology without
правда Чего не всегда или техника без
people understood, that is, yeah,
людей понял то есть ага
first of all Read Read this
во-первых Зачитай Зачитай этого
McGregor Conor
макгрегора конора
McGregor Now let's see, let's not be
макгрегора Сейчас посмотрим давай нене
interested, maybe it's really there, maybe
интересно может действительно там может
he really refers to some
он действительно ссылается на какие-то
data, now
данные сейчас
let's see  automatically the
посмотрим автоматически
EU don’t just give me a link to
ЕС не просто давай вот ссылку на
some text Read Where so that it can be
какой-то текст Прочитай Где чтобы было
seen on the basis on the
видно на основани
basis I give that the situation Is somewhere
осно даю что ситуация Находится где-то
between catastrophic It’s huge it’s
между катастрофической Огромно это
just just his words Yes, any
просто вот просто слова его Да любой
journalist can say
журналист может что угодно говорить
anything but what is there is some-  then
онова чего вот есть какое-то
comparison is all Look, these are just
сравнение это всё Смотри это просто
words numbers Come on
слова числа Давай
numbers Come on numbers you have
числа Давай числа есть у тебя числа
some numbers he will say now he will
какие-то он сейчас скажет он сейчас
say now Well, let’s rewind where
скажет Ну давай вот перемотай где будут
the numbers will be I’m interested
числа мне интересно потому
because I operate with specific numbers oh there’s
что я оперирую конкретными числами
some kind of
оь каким-то
gap here I’m shorter than Kona  Varvara
пролом вот я короче Кона Варвара
listened briefly and he said something
послушал короче и он что-то там
Say as much as he says And where is
Говори сри сколько говорит А где
the fact where is the fact Well, then it continues
факта где факта Ну дальше продолжается
no number Tell me against what was the
хо числа скажи давай проти что было
number Let's fry you FSB agent class
число Давай прожарил тебя фсбшник клас
because I can confirm everything I say with a
потому что я всё что говорю я могу
document here we go Yes there is
подтвердить докумен вот мы заходим Да
visible  based on this and that,
есть видно на основании того и того у
you have some abstract, short words
вас какие-то абстрактные короче слова
somewhere, you heard something, you didn’t even
где-то что-то слышал ты же даже не
listen to him Yes, because you would have known
слушал его Да потому что ты бы знал
what numbers he voiced and where he
какие числа он озвучивал и где он там
voiced them Yes, how many minutes is he in the video
озвучивал Да сколько минут е он видео
there is a lot of stuff  how much he broadcasts how
там вещ скоко сколько он вещает сколько
much he broadcasts Come on, in short, whoever you want Look for yourself
Давай короче кто хотите Посмотрите сами
about No, whoever watch Look whoever you want
о Не ну кто смотрите Смотри кто хотите
Look at Konon Varvara Konon
Посмотрите конона Варвара конона
McGregor Douglas in short yes Dude, you
макгрегора дугласа короче да Чувак ты
crap, I understand you in the face
обосрался понимаешь я тебя пово мордой
of [ __ ] completely pony
по говну полностью пони
because I poked you, I poked you Look,
потому я тебя ткнул я тебя ткнул Смотри
I  In short, I turn off the sound and the finals,
я тебя короче отключаю звук и финали
look, I poked you with all the facts Yes,
смотри я тебя ткнул по всем фактам Да
counter-offensive, counter-offensive, you say, I
контрнаступ контрнаступ ты говоришь те я
poked you in artillery, you extend five times,
тебя ткнул в артиллерии вы в пять раз
and in armored vehicles, oryx, in
простирается да в бронетехнике орикс
short, confirms in 7 days 118
короче подтверждает вот за 7 дней 118
Russians against 25 Ukrainians, the same
российских против 25 украинских та же
thing, I can’t hear you  I muted you, you
само я тебя не слышу я тебя отключил
sucker, like yes, about human
звук [__] типа да вот и про людские
losses, the same thing you have five times
потери также самое у вас в пять раз
more equipment, but from somewhere we have more
больше техники но откуда-то у нас больше
human losses, how did I
человеческих потерь как всё я тебе
tell
раскатал Я люблю раскатывать фсбшников
you
Да у тебя аж хлебало изменилось Да
everything?  we give you a
серьёзный пошл вон давай мы тебя
nofi high, put you plus Who got high in the
нофи кайф поставь ты плюс Кто кайфанул в
central government of the collapse based on the fact of the central government of the FSB officer Yes, we
цго развала по факта цго фсбшника Да мы
were together with him
з ним были
on the topic of the training manual How your counter-offensive in
тема методичка Как ваш контрнаступ
short crashed just about the facts that are
короче разбилась просто об факты которые
priests Yes, good, yes good I love
попы Да хорошо да хорошо Я так люблю вот
these manipula so much Yes, they show like five
эти манипуля Да показывают вот типа пять
there  broken pictures of five broken ones it
там разбитых фотки пятерых разбитых это
doesn’t show anything yes what are these five
ничего не показывает да что это за пять
yes Or is it in one day or two or
да Или это за один день или за два или
even one yes And how many died
даже за один да А сколько там погибло
there maybe it was you who destroyed five and yours
там может это вы пять уничтожили а ваших
were destroyed 100 Yes because you were
уничтожили 100 Да из-за того что вы
breaking in yes  that is, this is what you need to
ломились да то есть вот что надо
show the loss ratio and not
показывать соотношение потеря а не
just a photograph, here is your damaged Tank
просто фотография вот ваш подбитый Танк
and what does this say? Yes, you have 20
и что Это говорит Да вот у вас 20
damaged about 20 against one, this says
подбитых о 20 против одного это говорит
so all the facts Yes, they are just
поэтому все факты Да они просто
crap, yes Conan McGregor there chi Who is
обсираются да Конан МакГрегор там чи Кто
there Douglas Okay show me  Well, no, I’m not
там Дуглас Хорошо покажи я ж не я не
afraid, if it really happened, I would
боюсь если действительно было я бы
discuss it, find it, you know, that’s
обговорить найти понимаете У них вот там
how it works for them. Russian Propaganda
как работает Российская Пропаганда
Skobeev says as he said blah blah blah
скобеева говорит как сказал бла-бла-бла
and something shorter he said and on the basis of
и что-то короче он сказал а на основании
what even he said They don’t listen to them they were
чего даже он сказал Они не слушат им
told  TV and they drag it
сказали по телевизору и они это тащат
this [ __ ] you know from your ears so it’s
это [__] знаешь по своим ушам поэтому
cool I liked it I got a kick out of the
круто Мне понравился Я кайфанул от
collapse of this FSB guy just a thrill Slava
развала этого фсбшника просто кайф Слава
Ukraine write to th Telegram right now axis
украини пись на й Telegram прям зараз
VN
ось ВН
apok tse more and more respectfully YouTube taking
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through skarg or to your ban and even more
нас через скарг ор в твый бан и дуже
I don’t show a lot of video to people at all times, I don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams for this purpose, so
показуе информация про стримы тому для
that Mali can write an operational link
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
right away, but in the meantime, in
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в
telegrams OKM, the video is also tezh Tsikava and
телеграми окм вдео ще теж цикава и
Korisna information and we are guilty of you
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
trimati
тримати
postiyny operational link,
постийний оперативный звязок
regardless of that, show you  protse
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava ukraini
YouTube Слава украини
write Ne
пиши Ne